17
00:20:55,000 --> 00:21:00,000
本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译
仅供学习使用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
彼以国士待我 我以国士待之
用过免费优质字幕服务 而又有能力的人
有义务将这个免费服务做下去
若有心加入我们
请联系QQ群：428872140

18
00:03:06,520 --> 00:03:11,200
超级商店

19
00:03:08,650 --> 00:03:11,200
第一季 第一集
大家字幕组 欢乐出品

20
00:03:14,000 --> 00:03:16,000
翻译    树树   马小云

21
00:03:16,000 --> 00:03:18,000
翻译    树树   马小云

22
00:03:18,000 --> 00:03:20,000
翻译    累   康佳Cage

23
00:03:20,000 --> 00:03:22,000
翻译    累   康佳Cage

24
00:03:22,000 --> 00:03:24,000
校对    My Life

25
00:03:24,000 --> 00:03:26,000
校对    My Life

26
00:03:26,000 --> 00:03:28,000
时间轴    六级求过的风   小小   大梅子

27
00:03:28,000 --> 00:03:30,000
时间轴    六级求过的风   小小   大梅子

28
00:03:30,000 --> 00:03:32,000
特效    嵬森

29
00:03:32,000 --> 00:03:34,000
特效    嵬森

30
00:03:34,000 --> 00:03:36,000
压制    冰岛

31
00:03:36,000 --> 00:03:38,000
压制    冰岛

32
00:00:00,800 --> 00:00:02,860
美国超级商店
The American superstore.

33
00:00:03,060 --> 00:00:04,350
一站式购物
One-stop shopping

34
00:00:04,380 --> 00:00:07,600
只有你想不到 没有你买不到
For everything you could ever want or need.

35
00:00:07,720 --> 00:00:09,420
你想变得更瘦一点吗?
Do you want to be thinner?

36
00:00:09,950 --> 00:00:11,170
还是胖一点?
Fatter?

37
00:00:11,820 --> 00:00:12,970
更开心?
Happier?

38
00:00:13,580 --> 00:00:14,910
还是更悲伤?
Sadder?

39
00:00:15,090 --> 00:00:17,650
你在寻找友谊吗?
Are you looking for friendship?

40
00:00:17,980 --> 00:00:19,390
还是想自己一个人静静?
Or solitude?

41
00:00:19,770 --> 00:00:21,740
还是你在寻找爱情?
Or even love?

42
00:00:21,840 --> 00:00:24,120
这个实际上只是一块氧化锆山寨货
That's actually a cubic zirconia knockoff.

43
00:00:24,160 --> 00:00:25,370
叫水钻
It's called plasticlear.

44
00:00:25,400 --> 00:00:26,840
8美元的那种呢?
What happened to the $8 ones?

45
00:00:26,910 --> 00:00:28,580
那种卖光了 抱歉
We're all sold out of those, sorry.

46
00:00:28,600 --> 00:00:30,460
但这个也就贵了2美元啊
But this one's only $2 more.

47
00:00:30,700 --> 00:00:31,560
我明白了
I get it.

48
00:00:31,710 --> 00:00:32,830
你们拿便宜的珠宝做广告
You advertise the cheap jewelry

49
00:00:32,860 --> 00:00:33,690
把屌丝们都吸引过来
To get the suckers in the door,

50
00:00:33,730 --> 00:00:35,040
然后再推销贵的东西
Then you push the expensive stuff.

51
00:00:35,080 --> 00:00:36,810
好吧 我不会用 "屌丝" 这个词
Well, I wouldn't use the word "suckers,"

52
00:00:36,920 --> 00:00:38,220
也不会用 "贵"
Or "expensive,"

53
00:00:38,350 --> 00:00:39,640
也不会用 "珠宝"
Or "jewelry."

54
00:00:41,620 --> 00:00:42,410
好吧
Fine.

55
00:00:42,490 --> 00:00:44,290
我急着要去排队买香烟了
I got to stand in line for cigarettes anyhow.

56
00:00:44,340 --> 00:00:44,880
好极了
Great.

57
00:00:44,920 --> 00:00:48,410
祝你和你的未婚妻百年好合...
I hope you and your fiancée are very happy together...

58
00:00:49,500 --> 00:00:51,280
...不生小崽子祸害大众
And that you don't procreate.

59
00:00:51,560 --> 00:00:53,050
- 格伦 - 干啥?
- Glenn. - Huh?

60
00:00:53,200 --> 00:00:54,540
我需要休息一下 帮助恢复我的心理健康
I'm taking a mental-health break.

61
00:00:54,580 --> 00:00:56,590
好的 开心点吧
Okay. Have fun now.

62
00:00:56,750 --> 00:00:57,930
好好想想
Reflect.

63
00:00:58,980 --> 00:01:02,500
现在来看看你的新求职表
Just checking over your new hire forms.

64
00:01:02,540 --> 00:01:04,450
美国公民 好极了
American citizen. Nice.

65
00:01:05,100 --> 00:01:06,220
没有孩子
No dependents.

66
00:01:06,260 --> 00:01:07,870
我也没有 除非你把我的鸟也算上
Me neither, unless you count my birds.

67
00:01:09,280 --> 00:01:11,060
只不过这张表上没说
It just doesn't say anywhere on here

68
00:01:11,100 --> 00:01:12,860
你是不是已经有女朋友了
if you've got a girlfriend.

69
00:01:13,770 --> 00:01:15,310
可我没有... 这个要填吗?
I didn't... Is there a space for that?

70
00:01:15,340 --> 00:01:16,260
这里有一栏说了
There's this section here:

71
00:01:16,280 --> 00:01:17,530
"还有别的我们需要知道的事吗?"
"is there anything else we should know?"

72
00:01:17,560 --> 00:01:19,130
有些人会自觉写上有没有女朋友
Some people like to volunteer it.

73
00:01:19,570 --> 00:01:22,280
哦 啊 那就也没有
Oh. Um...Then also no.

74
00:01:22,300 --> 00:01:23,530
- 没有 - 没有
- No. - No.

75
00:01:23,580 --> 00:01:26,380
好 那么 我就稍稍帮你添一笔
Okay, well, i will just jot that down, then.

76
00:01:26,430 --> 00:01:28,250
你是异性恋对吧?
But you are heterosexual, right?

77
00:01:28,290 --> 00:01:30,590
你可以问这个吗?
Is...Are you allowed to ask that?

78
00:01:31,000 --> 00:01:31,840
不可以
No.

79
00:01:36,380 --> 00:01:37,180
机智啊
Smart.

80
00:01:37,250 --> 00:01:39,500
我们总是把最好的卷纸放在最中间
We always keep the best rolls right in the middle.

81
00:01:41,660 --> 00:01:43,330
哦 等一下 让我来帮你
Oh, wait. No, no, no. Let me help you with that.

82
00:01:43,360 --> 00:01:44,280
哦 不 不 不 我没事
Oh, no, no, no. I'm fine.

83
00:01:44,310 --> 00:01:45,480
没关系的 我在这里工作
It's fine, I work here.

84
00:01:45,520 --> 00:01:46,360
这是 是我的
It's, like, my--

85
00:01:46,400 --> 00:01:48,130
帮助顾客就是我的工作 所以
It's my job to help customers, so.

86
00:01:48,160 --> 00:01:49,530
你在这里工作?
You work here?

87
00:01:49,890 --> 00:01:50,700
什么时候开始的?
Since when?

88
00:01:51,220 --> 00:01:52,130
就现在开始
Since right now.

89
00:01:52,180 --> 00:01:54,120
实际上这是我工作的第一天
I'm--it's actually my first day.

90
00:01:54,160 --> 00:01:55,360
- 哦 - 我知道
- Oh. - I know.

91
00:01:55,730 --> 00:01:56,990
我看起来就不像是那种
I don't seem like the kind of person

92
00:01:57,020 --> 00:01:58,410
会在这种地方工作的人
who would work in a place like this.

93
00:01:59,940 --> 00:02:01,800
是啊 所以我刚才那么惊讶
Yeah, that's why i was so surprised.

94
00:02:01,830 --> 00:02:03,260
我都惊得就像"搞毛啊?"
I was like, "what?"

95
00:02:03,300 --> 00:02:04,430
- "搞毛?" - "他?"
- "what?" - "him?"

96
00:02:04,470 --> 00:02:06,170
他做错了什么要在这里收拾卫生纸?
"what's he doing cleaning up toilet paper?"

97
00:02:06,220 --> 00:02:08,090
我想这是因为 你就是拥有那种
I think it's because you just--you have this

98
00:02:08,120 --> 00:02:11,710
一看就很聪明 受过教育的知识分子气质
very intelligent, educated, more cultured quality,

99
00:02:11,760 --> 00:02:12,830
我的意思是 相比较她...
I mean, compared to...

100
00:02:12,860 --> 00:02:14,120
是啊 哦 嘿
Yeah. Oh, hey.

101
00:02:14,690 --> 00:02:16,370
听着 我明白你是在恭维我
Look, i get that you're complimenting me,

102
00:02:16,410 --> 00:02:17,890
但是这可能听起来有点儿居高临下
But it might sound a little condescending,

103
00:02:17,930 --> 00:02:18,780
所以 你懂的
So, you know...

104
00:02:18,820 --> 00:02:19,580
哦 是啊 谢谢了
Oh, yeah, thanks.

105
00:02:19,630 --> 00:02:21,480
不 我可不想听起来居高临下
No, i wouldn't want to sound condescending

106
00:02:21,570 --> 00:02:23,140
尤其是在某个在这里工作的人面前
In front of somebody who works here.

107
00:02:23,340 --> 00:02:23,930
正是
Right.

108
00:02:26,370 --> 00:02:28,040
嘿 我能去走开两分钟吗?
Hey, can i run out for two minutes?

109
00:02:28,090 --> 00:02:29,770
这个家伙正在踢我的膀胱
This thing is kicking my bladder

110
00:02:29,790 --> 00:02:30,720
好像我的膀胱欠他钱了
Like it owes him money.

111
00:02:30,760 --> 00:02:31,840
哦 你知道 我其实不管...
Oh, you know what, i'm actually not in charge...

112
00:02:31,880 --> 00:02:34,030
好的 当然了 我会把卡莉从快捷结账通道叫过来顶班
Yes, of course. I'll take Carly off express.

113
00:02:34,050 --> 00:02:36,000
直到薇薇安回来 你想去多久就去吧
until Vivian come back, so take as long as you need.

114
00:02:36,030 --> 00:02:37,530
啊 谢谢你
Ah, thanks.

115
00:02:42,180 --> 00:02:43,040
小贴士
Little tip:

116
00:02:43,100 --> 00:02:44,570
别让这里其余的工作人员
Don't let the other workers here

117
00:02:44,610 --> 00:02:46,420
知道你比他们好了多少
know how much better than them you are.

118
00:02:46,620 --> 00:02:47,740
他们讨厌这个
They hate that.

119
00:02:47,800 --> 00:02:49,110
我也不知道为什么 也许是因为
I don't know why, maybe because

120
00:02:49,140 --> 00:02:50,780
这听上去有点居高临下
it sounds condescending.

121
00:02:53,080 --> 00:02:53,940
欢迎你
Welcome.

122
00:02:57,520 --> 00:02:58,570
我...
I'm...

123
00:03:00,200 --> 00:03:02,190
不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no!

124
00:03:10,420 --> 00:03:11,880
好了 同志们 听好了
All right, campers, listen up.

125
00:03:11,890 --> 00:03:13,400
我有一个重要的消息要宣布
I've got an important announcement.

126
00:03:13,440 --> 00:03:16,190
这是通用的治疗鼻塞的药
This is your garden variety generic decongestant.

127
00:03:16,300 --> 00:03:18,810
这是冰毒 看清楚了?
And this is crystal meth, okay?

128
00:03:18,840 --> 00:03:22,210
那些瘾君子用这个 造出了这个
The tweakers use this to make this.

129
00:03:22,240 --> 00:03:25,150
所以别卖他们这个 他们就做不出这个
So stop selling them this, so they can't make this.

130
00:03:25,180 --> 00:03:27,600
那个男人跟我说他得了重感冒
That guy told me he had a really bad cold.

131
00:03:27,630 --> 00:03:29,600
他买了35盒 夏安
He was buying 35 boxes, Cheyenne.

132
00:03:29,640 --> 00:03:31,350
你该意识到这是个危险的信号了好吗?
That should have been a red flag, okay?

133
00:03:31,400 --> 00:03:32,320
动动脑子
Use your noggin.

134
00:03:32,530 --> 00:03:34,140
让我们谢谢迪娜
Let's thank Dina

135
00:03:34,180 --> 00:03:35,920
为我们带来的精彩小贴士
for that helpful tip of the day.

136
00:03:35,960 --> 00:03:36,760
谢谢 迪娜
Thank you, Dina.

137
00:03:36,810 --> 00:03:37,940
难道只有我觉得她拿着一袋冰毒
Am I the only one that thinks it's weird

138
00:03:37,970 --> 00:03:39,960
瞎晃悠是很奇怪的事吗?
that she walking around with a bag of crystal meth?

139
00:03:40,050 --> 00:03:40,650
嘿 听着
Hey, listen.

140
00:03:40,690 --> 00:03:43,400
我觉得 我觉得肯定有什么误会
I--i think there might have been a misunderstanding.

141
00:03:43,430 --> 00:03:45,810
我不是个精英主义者 所以
I'm not an elitist, so...

142
00:03:45,860 --> 00:03:47,920
哦 精英主义者? 那是什么?
Oh, elitist? What is that?

143
00:03:47,970 --> 00:03:50,200
就是一个人 觉得他比别人都好...
Like, a person who thinks they are better than...

144
00:03:50,590 --> 00:03:52,700
你知道精英主义是什么意思
You know what elitist means.

145
00:03:52,740 --> 00:03:53,760
哦 是啊
Oh, yeah.

146
00:03:53,790 --> 00:03:55,740
他们在公立学校里教过我们
They learnt that to us in public school.

147
00:03:55,780 --> 00:03:58,360
无论如何 我很自豪地
Anyway, i am so proud

148
00:03:58,430 --> 00:04:03,930
欢迎两位新来的小天使加入我们的的云九大家庭
to welcome two new angels to our cloud 9 family.

149
00:04:04,090 --> 00:04:05,920
你们快自我介绍一下吧
Why don't you introduce yourselves?

150
00:04:06,570 --> 00:04:07,380
好的
Okay.

151
00:04:07,450 --> 00:04:08,480
大家好
Hello, everyone.

152
00:04:08,510 --> 00:04:10,590
我叫乔纳
I am Jonah.

153
00:04:11,140 --> 00:04:12,800
我很激动能来这里
And I am-- i am excited to be here.

154
00:04:12,860 --> 00:04:14,120
这一定会很有趣的 所以...
This is gonna be fun, so...

155
00:04:15,010 --> 00:04:17,930
我叫马特奥·费尔南多·阿基诺·李旺诺
My name is Mateo Fernando Aquino Liwanag,

156
00:04:17,950 --> 00:04:20,230
我来这里是为了成就一番事业
And I'm here to make something of myself.

157
00:04:20,270 --> 00:04:21,920
展开双翅
Spread my wings

158
00:04:23,040 --> 00:04:24,860
飞得更远 飞得更高
See how far i can fly.

159
00:04:24,910 --> 00:04:27,300
谢谢 谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you.

160
00:04:27,360 --> 00:04:30,610
我也是 想看看我能飞多远
Yeah, I, too, would like to see how far I can fly.

161
00:04:33,490 --> 00:04:34,600
所以...
So...

162
00:04:35,490 --> 00:04:36,620
- 省省吧 - 谢谢
- Saved it. - Thank you.

163
00:04:36,650 --> 00:04:39,880
好了 我通常都会引用圣经里的
Now, I used to end these meetings

164
00:04:39,920 --> 00:04:42,360
名言金句来结束这类会议
with some wisdom from the good book.

165
00:04:42,380 --> 00:04:44,570
但是有人把我举报到了公司去
But then someone reported me to corporate.

166
00:04:44,600 --> 00:04:45,690
没错啊 老娘干的
Heck yeah, I did.

167
00:04:45,730 --> 00:04:47,990
听着 我也是个基督徒 但是在这个房间里
Look, i'm a christian too, but in these four walls,

168
00:04:48,030 --> 00:04:50,310
《员工行为准则》就是我的圣经
My bible is the employee code of conduct.

169
00:04:50,540 --> 00:04:51,680
我们都会为了这个感谢你的
We all thank you for it.

170
00:04:51,720 --> 00:04:53,150
呵呵 别客气
Yeah, you're welcome.

171
00:04:53,450 --> 00:04:54,620
我为你祈祷 迪娜
I pray for you, Dina.

172
00:04:54,660 --> 00:04:55,550
我也为你祈祷 格伦
I pray for you, too, Glenn.

173
00:04:55,580 --> 00:04:56,620
不 我现在就在祈祷
No, i'm praying right now.

174
00:04:56,670 --> 00:04:57,720
我狠狠地祈祷
I'm praying so hard.

175
00:04:58,020 --> 00:04:59,150
我在更狠地祈祷
I'm praying harder than you.

176
00:04:59,210 --> 00:05:00,010
我知道怎么祈祷
I know how.

177
00:05:00,090 --> 00:05:03,120
所以为了欢迎我们的新员工...
So to welcome our new employees...

178
00:05:05,680 --> 00:05:06,580
欢迎
Welcome.

179
00:05:06,850 --> 00:05:08,800
欢迎来到云九
Welcome to Cloud 9.

180
00:05:08,920 --> 00:05:10,650
这是我混的音
This is my jam.

181
00:05:15,690 --> 00:05:17,610
嘿 我们有什么员工培训吗?
Hey, do we have any kind of training?

182
00:05:17,640 --> 00:05:18,670
我只是在各个部门之间
I've just been wandering

183
00:05:18,720 --> 00:05:19,840
到处乱逛
from one department to another,

184
00:05:19,870 --> 00:05:21,580
假装看起来有目标的样子
trying to look like I have purpose.

185
00:05:21,630 --> 00:05:24,160
你要是搬个箱子就看起来更像了
It works better if you carry a box.

186
00:05:24,340 --> 00:05:25,240
看见了嘛?
There you go. See?

187
00:05:25,300 --> 00:05:26,210
你会学到东西的
You'll learn as you go.

188
00:05:26,260 --> 00:05:28,570
听着 小伙子 只有几件事你需要记住
Look, man, only a couple things to remember:

189
00:05:28,840 --> 00:05:31,170
别迟到 别偷东西
Always show up on time, don't steal,

190
00:05:31,230 --> 00:05:33,240
站在楼层管理员的角度考虑问题
and stay on the floor supervisor's good side.

191
00:05:33,310 --> 00:05:35,440
谁是楼层管理员?
The fl--who's the floor supervisor?

192
00:05:39,800 --> 00:05:41,430
我得去再拿一个箱子来
I got to go get another box.

193
00:05:43,740 --> 00:05:46,290
嘿 我们能重新来过吗?
Hey, can we-- can we start over?

194
00:05:46,360 --> 00:05:48,690
我... 乔纳 如你所见
I'm... Jonah, as you know.

195
00:05:48,720 --> 00:05:50,190
而你叫蕾莫娜
And you're Ramona.

196
00:05:50,240 --> 00:05:51,880
不 那不是我的名字
Nope, that is not my name.

197
00:05:52,010 --> 00:05:53,980
我只是不喜欢随便哪个陌生人都叫我的名字
I just don't like random strangers using my name

198
00:05:54,020 --> 00:05:54,860
好像我们很熟一样
like we're buddies.

199
00:05:54,900 --> 00:05:56,620
好吧 这就像妓女
Right, like how hookers

200
00:05:56,650 --> 00:05:58,270
不喜欢被亲小嘴儿一样
don't like to bekissed on the lips.

201
00:05:58,670 --> 00:06:00,270
你刚才是在拿我和妓女做比较吗?
Did you just compare me to a hooker?

202
00:06:01,550 --> 00:06:02,440
不是
No.

203
00:06:02,890 --> 00:06:03,880
你看起来无所事事啊
You look bored.

204
00:06:03,920 --> 00:06:05,130
我来帮帮你吧
Let me help youwith that.

205
00:06:05,160 --> 00:06:07,830
所有的电子产品要打7.5折
All electronics aresupposed to be 25% off,

206
00:06:07,880 --> 00:06:09,280
但是我们的零售管理系统出问题了
But our pos system is down.

207
00:06:09,340 --> 00:06:12,900
所以你就浏览一下 点击"重分配"
So you scan,hit "reassign,"

208
00:06:12,940 --> 00:06:14,730
"进入" "重置 确认 "
"enter," "override, yes,"

209
00:06:14,770 --> 00:06:17,300
"降价比例0.25 " "进入 确认 确认"
"reduce 0.25," "enter, yes, yes."

210
00:06:17,330 --> 00:06:18,350
你在走神
You are not paying attention.

211
00:06:18,370 --> 00:06:19,280
- 对不起哈 继续吧
- I'm sorry. Go ahead.

212
00:06:19,330 --> 00:06:21,690
- "确定 " "进入 确认" 明白了吗?
- "confirm," "enter, yes."got it?

213
00:06:21,730 --> 00:06:22,510
如果我猜你的名字
If i guessed your name,

214
00:06:22,540 --> 00:06:23,910
你能告诉我是不是猜对了吗?
would you tell meif i was right?

215
00:06:26,120 --> 00:06:27,260
拿着
Take this.

216
00:06:27,820 --> 00:06:30,070
天啊 太漂亮了!
Oh, it's so pretty!

217
00:06:30,120 --> 00:06:31,520
我会列一张清单的
I'll make a list.

218
00:06:32,570 --> 00:06:34,450
抱歉 女士
Oh, excuse me, miss.

219
00:06:34,500 --> 00:06:35,450
你知道大便软化剂
Do you know the difference

220
00:06:35,480 --> 00:06:37,210
和泻药之间的区别吗?
between a stool softener and a laxative?

221
00:06:37,260 --> 00:06:38,250
我待会就去找您 夫人
I'll be right with you, ma'am.

222
00:06:38,290 --> 00:06:39,860
夏安 发生了啥?
Cheyenne, what's going on?

223
00:06:39,900 --> 00:06:42,200
我的男朋友刚才向我求婚了
My boyfriend just asked me to marry him.

224
00:06:42,240 --> 00:06:43,100
我不想让便便变软
I don't want it soft.

225
00:06:43,130 --> 00:06:44,800
我只想把它拉出来
I want it out of me.

226
00:06:45,720 --> 00:06:47,520
你知道吗 我之前没意识到
You know, i hadn't realized earlier

227
00:06:47,560 --> 00:06:49,710
夏安就是你要求婚的那个幸运女孩
That cheyenne was the lucky girl you'd be proposing to.

228
00:06:49,760 --> 00:06:50,610
是的 我把她套牢了
Yeah, well,i knocked her up,

229
00:06:50,670 --> 00:06:51,860
我爸说我必须这样做
So my dad says i have to.

230
00:06:52,750 --> 00:06:54,040
太浪漫了
So romantic.

231
00:06:54,080 --> 00:06:54,980
这就是我的方式
That's how i do it, yo.

232
00:06:55,010 --> 00:06:56,260
百分之百的爱
100% love.

233
00:06:56,300 --> 00:06:57,540
膨胀剂?
Bulking agent?

234
00:06:57,610 --> 00:06:58,920
为啥我还想要它膨胀?
Why would I want more bulk?

235
00:07:00,050 --> 00:07:03,610
小夏 你还没答应他吧?
Chey, you didn't say yes,did you?

236
00:07:03,860 --> 00:07:05,440
为啥我不能答应呢?
Why wouldn't i say yes?

237
00:07:08,160 --> 00:07:09,560
夏安 看着我
Cheyenne, look at me.

238
00:07:09,600 --> 00:07:13,200
我理解你很轻易就会
I know how easy it is to get swept up in the...

239
00:07:13,230 --> 00:07:16,170
沉浸于这种浪漫的氛围
Romance of all of...This.

240
00:07:16,300 --> 00:07:17,220
但是...
But...

241
00:07:17,630 --> 00:07:19,750
慎重考虑 好吗?
Think it through, okay?

242
00:07:19,790 --> 00:07:21,230
别做会让自己会后悔的事
Don't do something you're gonna regret

243
00:07:21,250 --> 00:07:22,820
为了你的余生
For the rest of your life.

244
00:07:24,830 --> 00:07:25,910
好的 遵命
Yeah, okay.

245
00:07:26,620 --> 00:07:28,260
我会不拉直接睡的
I'm gonna go sleep on it.

246
00:07:38,210 --> 00:07:39,620
我想我拿下搞懂了
I think i got it down.

247
00:07:39,930 --> 00:07:41,870
无意冒犯 但你是我的竞争对手
No offense,but you're my competition,

248
00:07:41,930 --> 00:07:44,430
所以我实际上有那么一点点希望你失败
So i'm kind of actually rooting for you to fail.

249
00:07:44,670 --> 00:07:46,290
好吧 谢谢 再见
Okay, thanks. Bye.

250
00:07:52,250 --> 00:07:53,790
我搞明白了
I figured it out.

251
00:08:00,430 --> 00:08:02,350
我们需要新的货架放国旗帽
We need new shelf flags for the end caps,

252
00:08:02,400 --> 00:08:04,080
但是我们应该先检查一下各区
But we should check the DCPIS first,

253
00:08:04,130 --> 00:08:05,150
因为上次...
Because last time...

254
00:08:05,180 --> 00:08:06,770
发生了啥?
What is happening?

255
00:08:07,470 --> 00:08:09,190
是不是发生种族暴乱了?
Could it be a race riot?

256
00:08:09,240 --> 00:08:12,270
这种事情在早期很难看出端倪
It's so hard to tell in the early stages.

257
00:08:12,320 --> 00:08:13,860
或者是有狂欢?
Could be the rapture,

258
00:08:13,900 --> 00:08:15,300
那我为啥还在这待着?
But then why am i still here?

259
00:08:19,750 --> 00:08:21,220
我简直所向披靡啊
I am killing it over here.

260
00:08:21,240 --> 00:08:23,800
你只是把每件产品降价了25% 对吧?
You're only discounting everything 25%, right?

261
00:08:23,850 --> 00:08:26,670
- 是的 "浏览" "重分配" "确认" "重置"
- Yeah, "scan, "reassign," "yes," "override,"

262
00:08:26,700 --> 00:08:27,710
"确认" "重定价--"
"yes," "reprice--"

263
00:08:27,760 --> 00:08:29,580
- 减价 - 哈?
- Reduce. - Huh?

264
00:08:29,610 --> 00:08:30,910
降价比例0.25
Reduce 0.25.

265
00:08:30,960 --> 00:08:32,060
重定价0.25?
Reprice 0.25?

266
00:08:32,110 --> 00:08:33,860
那会把所有的价格变成25美分
That would change everything to 25¢.

267
00:08:40,900 --> 00:08:42,600
关门!
Shut it down!

268
00:08:42,640 --> 00:08:44,470
快把所有门都关上!
Shut it all down!

269
00:08:50,210 --> 00:08:53,170
如果你今天注册我们的购物者计划
If you sign up for our heavenly shoppers program today,

270
00:08:53,220 --> 00:08:54,980
你购买商品可以节省15%
You'll save 15% off your purchase,

271
00:08:55,010 --> 00:08:57,210
这将降低你的商品价格为22美分
Which would drop your price to 22¢.

272
00:08:57,240 --> 00:08:58,670
停止售卖所有商品!
Stop selling everything!

273
00:08:58,720 --> 00:08:59,660
关掉!
Shut it down!

274
00:08:59,710 --> 00:09:00,740
全部关掉!
Shut it all down!

275
00:09:00,760 --> 00:09:02,100
先生 你需要待在这儿
Sir, you need to stay right there.

276
00:09:02,120 --> 00:09:03,700
弗兰克 一个都不能离开!
Frank, nobody leaves!

277
00:09:03,760 --> 00:09:06,220
夫人! 夫人 我很抱歉
Ma'am! Ma'am, I'm sorry.

278
00:09:06,250 --> 00:09:07,620
我需要再重新检查这些物品
I'm gonna need to recheck some of these items.

279
00:09:07,690 --> 00:09:08,570
多谢 不了 再见
No thank you, buh-bye.

280
00:09:08,580 --> 00:09:10,040
不好意思 我不能就这样让你
I'm sorry, I can't just let you leave

281
00:09:10,080 --> 00:09:12,460
带着整篮的2毛5电子产品离开
With a whole basket full of 25¢ tech--Ow!

282
00:09:12,530 --> 00:09:14,140
我还有更多 小姐
I have more where that came from, lady!

283
00:09:14,170 --> 00:09:15,890
我不这么认为
Oh, I don't think so!

284
00:09:17,260 --> 00:09:18,400
顾客们请注意
Attention, shoppers.

285
00:09:18,440 --> 00:09:20,100
由于一位员工的错误操作
Due to an employee error,

286
00:09:20,130 --> 00:09:21,790
许多昂贵的电子产品
Very expensive electronics

287
00:09:21,800 --> 00:09:23,000
■

288
00:09:21,800 --> 00:09:23,000
笔记本电脑      0.25
手机                0.25
笔记本电脑      0.25
笔记本电脑      0.25
笔记本电脑      0.25
iPad                0.25
笔记本电脑      0.25
笔记本电脑      0.25
总价                2.00

289
00:09:21,840 --> 00:09:23,860
被标价为25美分
are pricing out at 25¢.

290
00:09:23,900 --> 00:09:26,240
系统正在修复 所以
This mistake is being corrected, so...

291
00:09:26,260 --> 00:09:27,080
快买起来!
Stock up quick!

292
00:09:27,120 --> 00:09:28,430
快 快 快
Go, go, go, go!

293
00:09:28,460 --> 00:09:31,560
我想说的是 这个标价不是2毛5
What I'm trying to say is, this is not 25¢.

294
00:09:32,190 --> 00:09:33,570
先生 不是的
Sir, no

295
00:09:34,240 --> 00:09:35,970
不是2 5 不是
No two-five, no.

296
00:09:36,660 --> 00:09:38,760
上了我的车就是我的了
It touched my car, it's mine!

297
00:09:38,810 --> 00:09:40,600
- 不是这么回事 - 就是这么回事
- That's not a thing. - It is a thing.

298
00:09:40,640 --> 00:09:42,490
我不想成为 "那种人"
I don't want to be "That guy,"

299
00:09:42,540 --> 00:09:45,810
但是如果你非要拿我的业绩和乔纳比的话
But if you had to compare my performance versus jonah...

300
00:09:45,840 --> 00:09:48,300
好吧
Uh, okay.

301
00:09:48,670 --> 00:09:50,350
你手脚最好麻溜点 小姑娘
Yeah, you better hurry up, girl.

302
00:09:50,380 --> 00:09:51,780
快拿下那台电视
You better get that tv.

303
00:09:51,810 --> 00:09:54,340
停下 停下 求你们了
Stop, stop! Please, I'm begging you!

304
00:09:54,370 --> 00:09:56,420
她真的 她真的是很漂亮 对
She's very--she's-- they're very pretty, yep.

305
00:09:56,460 --> 00:09:57,960
弗兰克!
Ow! Frank!

306
00:09:58,010 --> 00:09:59,200
你们不会想这样做的
Y'all don't want to do this.

307
00:09:59,230 --> 00:10:00,680
拜托了
Please!

308
00:10:01,720 --> 00:10:03,200
特价活动结束
Sale's over!

309
00:10:03,940 --> 00:10:06,880
完全没有必要去找出
There's no need to identify

310
00:10:06,920 --> 00:10:08,850
究竟是谁的错
whoever it is

311
00:10:08,890 --> 00:10:10,540
也没必要去归罪于谁
whose fault this was.

312
00:10:10,590 --> 00:10:12,770
大家可以从中吸取教训
We can all learn a lesson here.

313
00:10:12,810 --> 00:10:14,210
这教训能让乔纳
Would that lesson be not letting jonah

314
00:10:14,240 --> 00:10:16,080
别再私自重新定价了吗?
reprice inventory in the future?

315
00:10:16,910 --> 00:10:18,590
或许 会吧
It might be, yes.

316
00:10:18,610 --> 00:10:20,930
那好吧 在准点到岗上
All right. Punctuality.

317
00:10:21,180 --> 00:10:22,680
我不能忍受迟到
I do not tolerate it,

318
00:10:22,690 --> 00:10:25,530
因为我也不能忍受自己迟到
because I do not tolerate it in myself.

319
00:10:25,550 --> 00:10:28,620
- 我脾气很暴躁 所以我很早就会来 - 喂
- I am an angry man, so I get places early...- Hey...

320
00:10:28,690 --> 00:10:31,950
他们允许员工约监督员吗?
Do they allow employees to date supervisors?

321
00:10:32,020 --> 00:10:33,490
不知道 怎么了
I don't know. Why?

322
00:10:34,130 --> 00:10:34,940
就好奇问下
Just curious.

323
00:10:34,980 --> 00:10:36,280
大家记好了
Let's always remember,

324
00:10:36,320 --> 00:10:38,800
顾客就是上帝
The customer is always right.

325
00:10:44,990 --> 00:10:48,120
嘿 你叫什么名字 快来看看
Hey, what's-your-name, check it out.

326
00:10:50,960 --> 00:10:52,710
我就在想为什么放几罐饮料
I was wondering what was taking so long

327
00:10:52,770 --> 00:10:54,100
能让你放那么久
to stack a few cans.

328
00:10:54,490 --> 00:10:56,580
我只是想对上次的事
I just--I wanted to reiterate

329
00:10:56,620 --> 00:10:58,370
再次说声抱歉
how sorry I am about before.

330
00:10:58,400 --> 00:11:01,120
要是如果顾客要买一罐姜汁酒
And when a customer wants a can of ginger root beer

331
00:11:01,160 --> 00:11:02,960
这一整排都会塌掉
and the whole thing collapses on top of them,

332
00:11:02,990 --> 00:11:04,440
到时候你会怎么想
how are you gonna feel then?

333
00:11:07,140 --> 00:11:08,740
我只是想找点乐子
I was just trying to have some fun.

334
00:11:08,830 --> 00:11:11,130
这可能是文化水平问题 但看看四周
This might be a cultural thing, but around here,

335
00:11:11,170 --> 00:11:13,480
你少搞砸一件事 这里就会更好一些
the less screwing everything up you do, the better.

336
00:11:13,550 --> 00:11:15,140
你说的是那些饮料还是定价的事
You talking about the cans or the pricing thing?

337
00:11:15,170 --> 00:11:16,640
你瞧你上班第一天
You see, the fact that it's your first day

338
00:11:16,690 --> 00:11:18,270
就搞砸了多少事
and there's already more than one option

339
00:11:18,300 --> 00:11:20,200
这可不是好事
of things you screwed up is not a good thing.

340
00:11:20,220 --> 00:11:21,660
好吧 我是犯了一些错
Okay, I've made some mistakes.

341
00:11:21,710 --> 00:11:23,010
我承认我做错了 但这不代表
I can admit that, but that doesn't mean

342
00:11:23,050 --> 00:11:25,260
我们不能在工作中找些乐子
we can't have a little fun at work, does it?

343
00:11:25,300 --> 00:11:26,880
或者去发现一些美丽瞬间吧?
or try and find some moments of beauty in the everyday?

344
00:11:28,240 --> 00:11:28,940
等下 不好意思
Wait, I'm sorry.

345
00:11:28,980 --> 00:11:31,450
你刚刚真的
Did you really just use the phrase "Moments of beauty,"

346
00:11:31,490 --> 00:11:33,020
说了 "美丽瞬间" 吗?
Like, conversationally?

347
00:11:33,050 --> 00:11:35,340
好吧 我知道 听起来是很俗 但是
Okay, yes, that's cheesy, but...

348
00:11:35,870 --> 00:11:37,550
记得电影《美国丽人》吗?
Do you remember "American beauty"?

349
00:11:37,730 --> 00:11:40,980
一个塑料袋都能美得让人窒息
Even a plastic bag can be breathtaking.

350
00:11:47,670 --> 00:11:49,360
真是让我大吃一惊呢
That really blew my mind.

351
00:11:49,640 --> 00:11:50,600
就像
Like...

352
00:11:51,960 --> 00:11:53,210
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I have goose bumps.

353
00:11:53,960 --> 00:11:55,560
反正我有感触
I felt something.

354
00:11:57,730 --> 00:11:58,730
我是乔纳
I'm jonah.

355
00:11:58,770 --> 00:11:59,840
第一天上班
It's my first day.

356
00:12:10,000 --> 00:12:12,090
好了 别动
Okay. Stay still.

357
00:12:12,120 --> 00:12:13,960
我不是经常画眼线
I don't usually wear eyeliner.

358
00:12:14,160 --> 00:12:15,680
偶尔骗下人 但是
Sharpie occasionally, but...

359
00:12:15,980 --> 00:12:19,310
那么 跟我说说你骗的那个人
So tell me about this special guy.

360
00:12:19,340 --> 00:12:20,420
好吧
Okay.

361
00:12:20,470 --> 00:12:21,920
男的 白种人
Male, caucasian,

362
00:12:22,000 --> 00:12:24,650
没有明显的伤疤和纹身
No discernible scars or tattoos.

363
00:12:26,000 --> 00:12:27,460
听起来很美好啊
Sounds dreamy.

364
00:12:27,650 --> 00:12:28,570
对啊
Yeah.

365
00:12:28,970 --> 00:12:30,480
你懂得 说到男孩们
You know, speaking of boys,

366
00:12:30,510 --> 00:12:32,510
我要做一个重大决定
I've got a pretty big decision to make.

367
00:12:32,740 --> 00:12:34,030
我男朋友 他
My boyfriend, he

368
00:12:34,070 --> 00:12:35,870
我很高兴我们能彼此交心
I'm glad we could bond like this.

369
00:12:37,370 --> 00:12:38,380
谢谢
Thank you.

370
00:12:41,470 --> 00:12:42,660
不好意思 不好意思
Excuse me, excuse me!

371
00:12:42,690 --> 00:12:43,300
嗨
Hi!

372
00:12:43,660 --> 00:12:45,340
我把试衣间里的所有东西全挂起来了
I hung up everything that was in the dressing rooms,

373
00:12:45,390 --> 00:12:47,790
还把它们根据风格 颜色和大小
and I organized it by style, color, size,

374
00:12:47,860 --> 00:12:49,600
以及设计师的相似性分了类
and relevance of designer.

375
00:12:49,650 --> 00:12:51,610
哇 干得好
Wow. Good job.

376
00:12:52,180 --> 00:12:53,430
我享受努力工作
I enjoy hard work.

377
00:12:53,490 --> 00:12:54,690
就像我妈妈经常说的
It's just like my mom always said:

378
00:12:54,740 --> 00:12:57,170
"如果你不努力工作 圣婴耶稣都要哭"
"If you don't work hard, baby jesus will cry."

379
00:12:57,380 --> 00:12:57,950
好吧
Okay.

380
00:12:58,020 --> 00:12:59,240
我觉得在停车场里找乐子
I don't think I could be happy

381
00:12:59,280 --> 00:13:00,330
并不会让我开心
fooling around in the parking lot

382
00:13:00,350 --> 00:13:01,440
不像某些新来的
like the other new guy.

383
00:13:02,400 --> 00:13:04,120
慢点 这不公平
Slow down! This is not fair!

384
00:13:04,170 --> 00:13:06,500
你的轮胎比我的贵
You have more experience on wheels than I do!

385
00:13:06,560 --> 00:13:09,120
你自己残疾可不关我的事
Your disability is not my concern!

386
00:13:09,360 --> 00:13:10,530
在搞笑吗
Seriously?

387
00:13:10,590 --> 00:13:13,450
我让你做的是把购物车推走
The only thing I asked you to do was put the carts away.

388
00:13:13,490 --> 00:13:14,480
我正在推
That's what I'm doing,

389
00:13:14,540 --> 00:13:16,940
只是路程有点曲折
Just somewhat circuitously.

390
00:13:17,020 --> 00:13:18,890
一会见 傻缺
See you later, sucka!

391
00:13:18,910 --> 00:13:20,970
你是想被炒鱿鱼吗?
Are you trying to get fired?

392
00:13:21,020 --> 00:13:22,240
要是格伦看见了怎么办?
What if glenn sees this?

393
00:13:22,320 --> 00:13:24,260
我来也!
Coming through!

394
00:13:24,580 --> 00:13:26,000
让开
Move!

395
00:13:26,240 --> 00:13:27,460
这不算数
That doesn't count.

396
00:13:27,500 --> 00:13:29,490
冲啊 格伦
Go, glenn! Yeah!

397
00:13:31,420 --> 00:13:33,250
秀你一脸!
In your faces!

398
00:13:33,310 --> 00:13:34,770
打脸了吧!
Your faces!

399
00:13:35,680 --> 00:13:37,660
行了 我算是明白了
Okay. I get it.

400
00:13:37,710 --> 00:13:38,680
你是有趣的人
You're the fun guy.

401
00:13:38,730 --> 00:13:40,190
而我是个保守的呆子
I'm the stick in the mud.

402
00:13:40,420 --> 00:13:41,370
行啊 我也能玩起来
Well, I could be fun.

403
00:13:41,420 --> 00:13:42,920
- 我也能玩 来玩起来 - 当然你可以
- I could have fun,let's have fun.- Of course you can

404
00:13:42,970 --> 00:13:44,420
来玩吧
have fun.

405
00:13:44,470 --> 00:13:46,450
上班时间玩起来
We're playing at work.

406
00:13:47,050 --> 00:13:48,090
没刹车
No brakes!

407
00:13:48,140 --> 00:13:49,090
我没刹车啊!
I have no brakes!

408
00:14:03,650 --> 00:14:05,110
求和礼物
Peace offering.

409
00:14:05,150 --> 00:14:06,430
这是我在花园中心地上
Are those the flowers

410
00:14:06,470 --> 00:14:08,470
捡的花吗?
that I picked up off the floor of the garden center?

411
00:14:09,100 --> 00:14:10,420
是的
Yes.

412
00:14:12,190 --> 00:14:14,040
真是好看的垃圾花
They're beautiful trash flowers.

413
00:14:16,180 --> 00:14:18,180
我很抱歉 好吗?
Look, I'm sorry, okay?

414
00:14:18,230 --> 00:14:21,160
今天真是漫长的一天
I have been having a long day.

415
00:14:21,200 --> 00:14:23,930
其实过去十年的每一天都很漫长
Ten years of long days, actually.

416
00:14:26,870 --> 00:14:30,540
你知道吗 我每年开学打折季都要
You know, I stock these glow stars

417
00:14:30,620 --> 00:14:33,200
把这些亮星星摆上架
every single year for the back-to-school sale.

418
00:14:33,440 --> 00:14:35,140
然后下架
And then I take them down,

419
00:14:35,240 --> 00:14:37,080
然后上架万圣节库存
And I put up the Halloween inventory,

420
00:14:37,520 --> 00:14:39,410
接着是感恩节 圣诞节
and then Thanksgiving and Christmas

421
00:14:39,470 --> 00:14:42,000
情人节 复活节
and Valentine's day and Easter

422
00:14:42,030 --> 00:14:43,500
国庆节
and Fourth of July,

423
00:14:43,540 --> 00:14:45,620
然后又到开学季
and then back-to-school again.

424
00:14:47,290 --> 00:14:49,660
听起来的确挺无聊
That sounds incredibly not fun.

425
00:14:49,980 --> 00:14:52,190
我知道你为什么喜欢这了
I see why you love it here.

426
00:14:52,230 --> 00:14:53,900
这是个好工作
It's a good job.

427
00:14:54,480 --> 00:14:57,120
但明天将和今天一样
But tomorrow is gonna be just like today,

428
00:14:57,320 --> 00:14:58,260
我清楚这点
And I know that

429
00:14:58,320 --> 00:15:00,900
是因为今天就和昨天一样
because today is just like yesterday.

430
00:15:01,000 --> 00:15:03,980
所以... 有时候...
So... sometimes...

431
00:15:04,520 --> 00:15:07,340
真的很难寻找到那些美丽瞬间
It's just kind of hard to find those moments of beauty.

432
00:15:20,000 --> 00:15:21,340
顾客们请注意
Attention, shoppers.

433
00:15:21,480 --> 00:15:23,550
即使是超市也需要下班
Even a big box store has to close,

434
00:15:23,610 --> 00:15:24,900
时间快到了
And it's about that time.

435
00:15:24,940 --> 00:15:27,910
当潘多拉关上她的魔盒 只留了一件东西在里面
You know, when Pandora closed her famous box, there was only one thing left inside.

436
00:15:27,960 --> 00:15:31,570
希望
Hope.

437
00:15:31,570 --> 00:15:35,000
我想知道我们这里会留下什么
I wonder what will be left inside of this box.

438
00:15:35,040 --> 00:15:38,040
会是格蕾丝吗?
Could it be Grace?

439
00:15:38,090 --> 00:15:39,060
还是别了
I hope not.

440
00:15:39,090 --> 00:15:40,170
请格蕾丝的父母
If you're Grace's parents,

441
00:15:40,230 --> 00:15:43,140
来前台领走你们的孩子
please pick her up at customer service.

442
00:15:43,180 --> 00:15:44,660
我心血来潮
I took the initiative upon myself

443
00:15:44,700 --> 00:15:46,000
重新规划了玩具区域
to reorganize the toy section

444
00:15:46,050 --> 00:15:47,550
方便了成年顾客
for the convenience of adult shoppers.

445
00:15:47,550 --> 00:15:49,050
但这感觉实在是太奇怪了
It was just feeling overly whimsical.

446
00:15:49,100 --> 00:15:51,020
我想让你看看我做的东西
I want to show you something I've been working on.

447
00:15:51,070 --> 00:15:52,740
你在工作? 在哪?
Oh. You were working. Where?

448
00:15:52,770 --> 00:15:54,520
我所有部门都去了一趟
Because I've been in every single department,

449
00:15:54,560 --> 00:15:56,660
几小时都没见到你了
And I haven't seen you in a couple hours,

450
00:15:56,740 --> 00:15:58,200
除非你是在休息室
Unless you were in, like, the break room maybe.

451
00:15:58,240 --> 00:16:00,880
所有人趴下!
Everybody get down on the ground, now!

452
00:16:01,910 --> 00:16:03,650
趴下 趴下!
Get down, get down, get down!

453
00:16:03,680 --> 00:16:05,270
趴在地上!
Touch the ground!

454
00:16:05,760 --> 00:16:06,980
或滚出去!
Or get out!

455
00:16:07,040 --> 00:16:08,820
好了 冷静一下
All right, calm down.

456
00:16:08,850 --> 00:16:10,590
照我说的做 没人会受伤
Do what I say, and nobody gets hurt.

457
00:16:10,620 --> 00:16:12,040
我一直训练就是为了今天
This is what I trained for.

458
00:16:12,040 --> 00:16:14,140
我每分钟会杀个人
Now, I'm gonna start killing somebody every minute,

459
00:16:14,140 --> 00:16:16,240
除非...
Unless...

460
00:16:16,300 --> 00:16:18,510
除非夏安同意嫁给我
Unless you agree to marry me, Cheyenne.

461
00:16:18,510 --> 00:16:19,160
播放!
Hit it!

462
00:16:19,220 --> 00:16:20,480
卧了个槽?
Hey, what the ?

463
00:16:30,060 --> 00:16:36,850
"你愿意嫁给我吗?"
♪ I'll say, "will you marry me?" ♪

464
00:16:37,240 --> 00:16:39,080
我和这事无关
I had nothing to do with this.

465
00:16:39,130 --> 00:16:41,270
我知道
Yeah, I know.

466
00:16:41,270 --> 00:16:43,400
都是"油管"的错
This is the fault of youtube.

467
00:16:48,560 --> 00:16:50,480
听到你想在货架间走走
♪ Heard you want to walk down the aisle ♪

468
00:16:50,530 --> 00:16:51,700
你的宝宝需要一个父亲
♪ Your baby needs a daddy ♪

469
00:16:51,750 --> 00:16:52,700
我们在一起已有一段时日
♪ We've been bangin' for a while ♪

470
00:16:52,720 --> 00:16:54,980
我会对我所做所为负责
♪ All right, I pay the consequences of my actions ♪

471
00:16:55,020 --> 00:16:56,050
不要试着改变我
♪ Don't try to change me ♪

472
00:16:56,050 --> 00:16:57,330
因为我是实干家
♪ Cause I'm a man of actions ♪

473
00:16:58,060 --> 00:16:59,920
节目真不错
What a show.

474
00:16:59,960 --> 00:17:01,420
我要报告一件绿色代码的事件
I'm calling to report a code green in progress.

475
00:17:01,460 --> 00:17:02,790
重复 绿色代码
I repeat, code green.

476
00:17:02,830 --> 00:17:03,720
绿色代码是什么?
What's a code green?

477
00:17:03,760 --> 00:17:05,360
我上个月给你传真过一份代码清单的!
I faxed you a list of codes last month!

478
00:17:05,410 --> 00:17:06,440
有人质被劫持!
Hostage situation!

479
00:17:06,560 --> 00:17:08,300
赶紧派特警组过来!
You need to get SWAT down here right now!

480
00:17:08,300 --> 00:17:10,080
何时人们才会去学习
♪ When all these people gonna learn ♪

481
00:17:10,120 --> 00:17:11,520
我们都将受到打击
♪ We're gonna get burned ♪

482
00:17:11,550 --> 00:17:12,720
静静等待我们的时机
♪ Just waiting for our turn ♪

483
00:17:12,820 --> 00:17:15,170
感谢观看黑暗物质演出 各位
Yo, #blacklivesmatter, y'all.

484
00:17:16,180 --> 00:17:18,160
如果你们喜欢
Okay, if you like what you heard and saw,

485
00:17:18,210 --> 00:17:20,810
欢迎各个领域志同道合的朋友
I'm currently seeking representation in all areas.

486
00:17:20,840 --> 00:17:22,110
还有 我还做模特
Also, I do modeling,

487
00:17:22,140 --> 00:17:23,640
特别说明一下
So I'm just throwing that out there.

488
00:17:23,680 --> 00:17:25,710
好了 演出结束 圣路易斯
All right, peace out, St. Louis.

489
00:17:26,950 --> 00:17:28,730
- 小博 - 咋了?
- Bo. - What?

490
00:17:28,770 --> 00:17:30,680
哦 不好意思
Oh, my bad, yo.

491
00:17:33,560 --> 00:17:35,760
夏安·泰勒·李
Cheyenne Tyler Lee,

492
00:17:36,060 --> 00:17:37,690
你愿意嫁给我吗?
Will you marry me?

493
00:17:38,080 --> 00:17:40,430
或者像个混蛋一样拒绝我?
Or are you gonna be, like, a dick about it?

494
00:17:40,460 --> 00:17:42,350
他要开枪杀害人质了
Oh, I think he's about to shoot a hostage.

495
00:17:42,600 --> 00:17:44,160
- 我会尽全力阻止 - 你什么都别做
- I'll do what I can. - Don't do anything.

496
00:17:51,240 --> 00:17:52,280
这是什么?
What is this?

497
00:18:05,700 --> 00:18:07,250
美丽瞬间?
Moment of beauty?

498
00:18:17,080 --> 00:18:18,830
祝福夏安
To Cheyenne.

499
00:18:18,870 --> 00:18:20,000
干杯!
Cheers!

500
00:18:20,040 --> 00:18:22,250
尽管发生过"大学生饮用过量致死"事件
May your marriage be as sweet and colorful

501
00:18:22,290 --> 00:18:24,990
还是希望你的婚姻能
as this Cloud 9 brand caffeinated malt beverage,

502
00:18:25,020 --> 00:18:27,460
像云九牌饮料一样甜蜜多姿
without the recall for killing college students.

503
00:18:27,490 --> 00:18:30,630
我代表我和小博谢谢你们
Thank you, on behalf of myself and Bo.

504
00:18:31,850 --> 00:18:33,810
他的确让求婚很难忘
Well, he did make it memorable.

505
00:18:34,160 --> 00:18:35,150
这我承认
I'll give him that.

506
00:18:35,180 --> 00:18:36,850
大多数男的求婚时懒得去搞新意
I mean, most guys don't even bother

507
00:18:36,890 --> 00:18:38,650
说威胁要杀了你
threatening to kill you when they propose.

508
00:18:38,840 --> 00:18:40,270
你从来没有真正处于危险之中
You were never in any real danger.

509
00:18:40,310 --> 00:18:41,370
你知道的 对吧
You know that, right?

510
00:18:41,720 --> 00:18:43,640
我知道 只是个假抢劫
Yeah, I know. It was a fake robbery.

511
00:18:43,680 --> 00:18:46,080
这是一个装有气密装置
This is a high-velocity 440-grain lead

512
00:18:46,130 --> 00:18:47,790
和黄铜外壳的
flat-nose projectile with gas checks

513
00:18:47,850 --> 00:18:50,080
高速型440号平头铅弹
and a boxer-primed brass jacket.

514
00:18:50,240 --> 00:18:51,400
如果他靠近你十步之内
If he'd come within 10 feet of you,

515
00:18:51,660 --> 00:18:53,520
你会看到他的头像西瓜一样炸开
You would have seen his head explode like a watermelon.

516
00:18:54,770 --> 00:18:56,400
然后就该清理过道了
Cleanup on aisle.

517
00:18:56,460 --> 00:18:57,700
我都不会知道那是那条过道
I don't even know what aisle it is,

518
00:18:57,760 --> 00:18:59,590
因为牌子都被他的
cause his brains would be splattered

519
00:18:59,640 --> 00:19:00,610
脑浆糊住了
all over the sign.

520
00:19:04,830 --> 00:19:07,600
我希望我们可以工作时带首饰
You know, I wish that we could wear jewelry at work.

521
00:19:07,630 --> 00:19:09,780
它真是...
Oh, it's so...

522
00:19:10,440 --> 00:19:11,420
耀眼
Sparkly.

523
00:19:11,580 --> 00:19:13,200
你知道 我仔细想过你说的
You know, I thought about what you said

524
00:19:13,240 --> 00:19:16,110
关于别做什么会后悔的事
about not doing something that I might regret,

525
00:19:16,140 --> 00:19:20,940
但在那刻 在那些星星下
But then, in the moment, you know, under the stars,

526
00:19:21,000 --> 00:19:22,660
感觉很对
It just felt right.

527
00:19:22,720 --> 00:19:24,680
没有你 我肯定说不出我愿意
Without you, I would have never said yes,

528
00:19:24,720 --> 00:19:25,770
谢谢你
so thank you.

529
00:19:29,560 --> 00:19:32,560
我要去保释我的男朋友了
Well, I should go bail out my boyfriend now.

530
00:19:33,040 --> 00:19:35,880
应该说是未婚夫!
Or I mean bail out my fiancé!

531
00:19:37,160 --> 00:19:39,100
好了 我该走了
All right. I got to get going.

532
00:19:39,150 --> 00:19:40,150
各位晚安
Good night, everyone.

533
00:19:40,150 --> 00:19:42,120
晚安
Good night.

534
00:19:42,120 --> 00:19:44,470
等等
Hey, wait up.

535
00:19:44,500 --> 00:19:45,340
等一下
Wait up.

536
00:19:45,560 --> 00:19:48,140
我不是要...
Hey, I didn't mean to...

537
00:19:48,480 --> 00:19:50,500
在里面...
That, in there...

538
00:19:51,330 --> 00:19:52,710
我只是想让今天
I just wanted today

539
00:19:52,750 --> 00:19:55,100
和昨天不一样罢了
to feel different than yesterday.

540
00:19:55,130 --> 00:19:56,930
那你失败得很彻底啊
Well, then you completely failed,

541
00:19:56,930 --> 00:20:00,250
因为昨天发生了同样的事
Because that exact same thing happened yesterday.

542
00:20:02,820 --> 00:20:05,180
但... 谢谢你
But... thank you.

543
00:20:09,100 --> 00:20:09,510
好了
Okay.

544
00:20:09,560 --> 00:20:11,760
我真的要走了
I really do have to get going.

545
00:20:11,810 --> 00:20:13,260
明天班上见 乔纳?
See you at work tomorrow, Jonah?

546
00:20:13,300 --> 00:20:16,620
当然... 你叫啥来着
You certainly will... champ.

547
00:20:19,460 --> 00:20:21,420
艾米
Amy.

548
00:20:21,960 --> 00:20:24,880
很高兴认识你 艾米
Nice to meet you, amy.

549
00:20:30,080 --> 00:20:32,420
哥们 跟我们一起来吧
Yo, you should come with us, man.

550
00:20:32,440 --> 00:20:34,170
我们要去把人体模型的四肢扔到垃圾箱
We're gonna throw some mannequin limbs in the dumpster

551
00:20:34,220 --> 00:20:35,970
然后看捡破烂的是怎么被吓尿的
and watch garbage men freak out.

552
00:20:36,820 --> 00:20:38,140
听起来很棒
That sounds awesome.

553
00:20:38,170 --> 00:20:40,140
必须的
It is awesome.

554
00:20:40,180 --> 00:20:41,480
走吧
Come on.

